Guide to the Barbaralee Diamonstein-Spielvogel Collection, 1876-2020 and undated, bulk 1950-2020 RL.10006
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Art and Architecture Project Files, 1876-2016
  - Landmarks of New York, 1956-2017; 4
    - Landmarks of New York III, 1996-2001; 13
      - Correspondence with publisher (Abrams), 1997-1998 (Box 328)
      - Exhibition circulation: Chicago, 1999 (Box 329)
      - Exhibition circulation: Chicago to Bratislava, 1999 (Box 329)
      - Exhibition circulation: Chicago to London, 1998 (Box 329)
      - Exhibition circulation: Chicago to Paris, 1999 (Box 329)
      - Exhibition funding, 1997 (Box 329)
      - Exhibition labels, 1998 (Box 329)
      - Exhibition labels draft, circa 1998 (Box 329)
      - First galleys, 1997, 2 folders (Box 329)
      - Frames, APF Master Framemakers, 1998 (Box 329)
      - Historic district galleys, 1997 (Box 329)
      - Historic district maps, 1997 (Box 329)
      - Introduction, 1997 (Box 329)
      - New York Historical Society exhibition, 1997-1998 (Box 329)
      - New York School of Interior Design slide show, 1998 (Box 329)
      - Opening event, 1998 (Box 329)
      - Photocopies of prints, circa 1998 (Box 330)
      - Planning politics and neighborhoods, 1998 (Box 330)
      - Press kit, 1998 (Box 330)
      - Second galleys, 1997, 2 folders (Box 330)
      - Signing, circa 1998 (Box 330)
      - A Tale of Two Cities, 1999-2002 (Box 330)
      - A Tale of Two Cities: Bratislava, 2000 (Box 330)
      - A Tale of Two Cities: Chicago, 1999 (Box 330)
      - A Tale of Two Cities: Chicago/Prague, 1999 (Box 330)
      - A Tale of Two Cities: Gallery bar 2001 (Box 330)
      - A Tale of Two Cities: Landmarks of Chicago and New York, 2001-2004 (Box 330)
      - Vitrine text, circa 1998 (Box 330)
    - Landmarks of New York IV, 1998-2009; 14
      - Abrams correspondence, 2001 (Box 330)
      - Abrams correspondence, 2004 (Box 330)
      - Athens, Greece, 2008 (Box 330)
      - Book jacket, 2004 (Box 330)
      - Citations, 2006 (Box 331)
      - Corrections and additional designations, 1998 and 2004, 2 folders (Box 331)
      - Correspondence, 2003-2011, 6 folders (Box 331)
      - Correspondence and drafts, 2004 (Box 331)
      - Correspondence, notes, memos, 2004-2005 (Box 332)
      - Drafts, 2004, 4 folders (Box 332)
      - Galleys, oversize, 2004 (Box 380)
      - Drafts, correspondence, notes, miscellaneous, 2004 (Box 332)
      - Drafts, preliminary, 2004 (Box 333)
      - Drafts, venues, correspondence, 2005 (Box 333)
      - Exhibition, 2004 (Box 333)
      - Exhibition, 2005 (Box 333)
      - Exhibition, Cambodia, 2005 (Box 333)
      - Exhibition, correspondence, 2004 (Box 333)
      - Correspondence and draft, 2005 (Box 333)
      - Correspondence and draft, 2005-2006, 2 folders (Box 333)
      - Exhibition schedule, 2006 (Box 333)
      - Exhibition schedule, 2007 (Box 333)
      - Exhibition schedule, introduction, 2005 (Box 334)
      - Existing designations, 2009 (Box 334)
      - French, undated (Box 334)
      - Galleys, 2004 (Box 334)
      - Galleys, 2004, 2 folders (Box 381)
      - Galleys, 2005 (Box 334)
      - Galleys, 2005, 2 prints (Box 382)
      - Hellenic American Union clippings, 2007 (Box 334)
      - Hellenic American Union exhibition, 2007 (Box 334)
      - Hellenic American Union (Athens) presentation, visit, 2007 (Box 653)
      - Hellenic American Union exhibition, 2007, 2 posters (Box 381)
      - Clare Hertel Communications, 2004 (Box 334)
      - Clare Hertel Communications correspondence, 2005 (Box 334)
      - Clare Hertel Communications press packet, 2005 (Box 334)
      - International tour, U.S. Department of State, 2005-2006 (Box 334)
      - Introduction, 2001 (Box 334)
      - Japan, 2006 (Box 334)
      - London clippings, 2007 (Box 334)
      - Manuscript drafts, 2004, 4 folders (Box 335)
      - Miscellaneous correspondence, 2004 (Box 335)
      - National coverage, 2006 (Box 335)
      - New designation reports list, 1998 (Box 335)
      - New York Heritage Society exhibition, 2009, 2 folders (Box 335)
      - New York Social Diary publicity (David Patrick Columbia web site), 2005 (Box 336)
      - Photograph permission Vanouwenkerk, 2004 (Box 336)
      - Poster, oversize, circa 2004 (Box 381)
        5 copies
      - Press list, 2004 (Box 336)
      - Printing materials, 2005 (Box 336)
      - Project management, 2004 (Box 336)
      - Reception invitations, 2005 (Box 336)
      - RIBA exhibition, 2006-2007 (Box 336)
      - RIBA exhibition program, 2007 (Box 336)
      - Second draft, undated (Box 336)
      - Taiwan, 2006 (Box 336)
      - Text, 1998 (Box 336)
      - Tokyo presentation, 2006 (Box 336)
      - Tokyo posters, 2006 (Box 336)
      - Tokyo posters, 2006, 3 copies of poster (Box 381)
      - Travel correspondence, 2004 (Box 336)
      - Travel itinerary, 2006 (Box 336)
      - Updates, 2004 (Box 336)
      - Exhibit tour correspondence, 2007-2008 (Box 618)
      - Third Thursday presentation, Alliance for Downtown New York, Inc., 2008 April 4 (Box 653)
      - Landmarks presentation script, edits, 2005 (Box 653)
    - Landmarks of New York V, 2009-2013; 15
      - Acknowledgments, drafts, 2010 (Box 336)
      - Book cover, 2011 (Box 336)
      - Buffalo, New York, 2010 (Box 336)
      - Buffalo exhibition, 2010 (Box 336)
      - Correspondence, 2009 (Box 336)
      - Correspondence, 2010-2011 (Box 336)
      - Correspondence, 2011, 2 folders (Box 337)
      - Correspondence, 2011-2013 (Box 337)
      - Draft, 2010 (Box 337)
      - Draft copies, circa 2010 (Box 337)
      - Draft introduction, 2010 (Box 337)
      - Exhibition, 2010 (Box 337)
      - Exhibition, 2010-2011 (Box 337)
      - Exhibition images, 2011 (Box 337)
      - Exhibition images, 2005, 2001 and undated (Box 337)
      - Exhibition materials, 2010, folder 1 of 2 (Box 337)
      - Exhibition materials, 2010, folder 2 of 2 (Box 338)
      - Exhibition materials, 2011 (Box 338)
      - Exhibition opening, SUNY, 2011 (Box 338)
      - Exhibition photographs, 2012 (Box 338)
      - Exhibition [2012?], oversize photographic prints, 1980s, 7 prints (Box 382)
        Mostly St. Louis cityscapes from 1980s, including shots of Head House; there are two images of a NYC police station.
      - Exhibition posters and display materials, 2011-2013 (Box 338)
      - Exhibition materials, 2011-2013, oversize items: multiple panel captions, photographs, and printed materials (Box 179)
      - Exhibition materials, 2011-2013, 7 caption panels (Box 178)
      - Exhibition and program materials, LONY V, New York Historical Society, 2012-2013 (Box 604)
      - Exhibition and program materials, LONY V, New York Historical Society, 2012-2013 (Box 618)
      - Existing images, undated (Box 338)
      - Expenditures, 2010 (Box 338)
      - First pass pages, 2011 (Box 338)
      - First pass pages, 2011, 9 prints (Box 382)
      - French, 2012 (Box 338)
      - Galleys, 2011 (Box 338)
      - Galleys, 2011, 2 folders (Box 382)
      - Long Island Museum exhibition, 2012 (Box 338)
      - Manuscript, 2011 (Box 338)
      - Museum of the City of New York, 2009 (Box 338)
      - Parrish Art Museum, 2012 (Box 338)
      - Parrish Art Museum, 2012 (Box 618)
      - Interview with Robert Stern, at the Parrish Art Museum, Southampton, 2012 Aug. 9 (Box 148)
      - Photos and negatives, 2012 and undated (Box 338)
      - Photos and negatives, 2012 and undated (Box 618)
      - Preface and introduction drafts, 2010 (Box 338)
      - Press announcements, correspondence, 2012 (Box 338)
      - Professional photo sheets, undated (Box 339)
      - Schedule and writing, 2010-2011 (Box 339)
      - SUNY Press, email printouts, notes, 2010-2011 (Box 339)
      - SUNY Press, publicity materials, 2011 (Box 339)
      - Touring exhibition agreement, 2011 (Box 339)
      - The High Line drafts from conversation at Parrish Art Museum, 2012 (Box 148)
      - Assorted events and speech drafts, 2005-2011 (Box 618)
      - Exhibit tour speeches, drafts, and logistics, 2011-2012 (Box 618)
      - Book launch, 2011 (Box 618)
      - Permissions/drafts, 2011-2013 (Box 618)
      - Book proof, 2011; 5 folders (Box 626)
    - Landmarks of New York VI, 2010-2017; 16
      - Book typescripts, 2015 (Box 640)
      - 1st book proof, 2015-2016; 4 folders (Box 626)
      - 2nd book proof, 2016; 5 folders (Box 627)
      - Pages with errors from 2nd proof, 2015-2016 (Box 627)
      - Book proofs, 2015; 4 folders (Box 640)
      - Book proofs, 2016 (Box 634)
      - Correspondence, 2016 (Box 634)
      - Correspondence, 2016-2017 (Box 639)
      - Uncorrected proof, 2016 (Box 639)
      - Manuscript draft of index, 2015-2016; 2 folders (Box 627)
      - Manuscript draft of preface, 2015 (Box 627)
      - Bibliography, 2015-2016 (Box 627)
      - Individual designations: new entries, 2010-2011 (Box 627)
      - NYU Press catalog, 2016 (Box 627)
      - Contracts, marketing, correspondence, 2015-2016 (Box 627)
      - Exhibits, 2016-2017; 2 folders (Box 627)
      - Presentations, 2016-2017; 2 folders (Box 627)
      - Drawing of Diamonostein-Spielvogel giving a lecture at the NY Public Library, 2016 December (Oversize-folder 8)
    - Photographs and promotional materials, 1992-2006; undated; 17
      - Photographs and negatives, undated, Folders 1-4 of 5 (Box 339)
        Includes negatives, contact sheets, and many photographic prints, chiefly 8x10 inches, the majority captioned on the backs with photographer's name, landmark name and general location, and sometimes the year the photograph was taken. Most of these images are copyrighted.
      - Photographs and negatives, larger sizes, undated (Box 382)
      - Photographs and negatives, undated, Folder 5 of 5 (Box 340)
      - Calendar, 1992 (Box 599)
      - Albert Lorenz oversize drawings, undated, 4 items (Oversize-folder 1)
      - Posters, A Tale of Two Cities Exhibition, undated, 2 items (Oversize-folder 1)
      - Posters, undated, 3 posters (Box 597)
      - Posters, 2006 and undated, 5 posters (Box 597)
    - Potential Projects, 1960s-1990s; 18
      - 2 White Street House, undated (Box 340)
      - 7th Regiment Armory, 1967, 1983-1984 (Box 340)
      - 14 Wall Street, undated (Box 340)
      - 17 West 16th Street house, 1986 (Box 340)
      - 30th Police Precinct, undated (Box 340)
      - 69th Regiment Armory, 1987 (Box 340)
      - 72nd Street Subway kiosk, undated (Box 340)
      - 369th Regiment Armory, 1985 and undated (Box 340)
      - 409 Edgecombe Avenue Apartments, undated (Box 340)
      - 555 Edgecombe Avenue Apartments, undated (Box 340)
      - 574 Sixth Avenue Building (originally 57-59th West 16th Street), 1990 and undated (Box 340)
      - Abigail Adams Smith Museum, 1987 (Box 340)
      - Abyssinian Baptist Church and Community House, 1996 (Box 340)
      - Adaptation and renovation of older buildings, book, oversize, undated (Box 382)
      - Adaptation and renovation of older buildings, 2 photographs of unidentified location interior, undated (Box 340)
      - American Banknote Company Office Building, circa 1997 (Box 340)
      - American Express Company Building, 1997 (Box 340)
      - Beaver Building, 1997 (Box 340)
      - Church of Notre Dame, undated (Box 340)
      - Engine Company Number 7, Hook and Ladder Company, and Firehouse, undated (Box 340)
      - Drafts, research sources, 1980s (Box 340)
      - Equitable Building, undated (Box 340)
      - Felix Warburg Mansion, 1983-1987 (Box 340)
      - Felix Warburg Mansion, oversize newsletter 1983-1987 (Box 382)
      - Fire Engine Company Number 84, Hook and Ladder Company Number 34, undated (Box 340)
      - Ford Foundation Building, 1997 (Box 340)
      - George W. Bowdoin Stable, undated (Box 340)
      - George W. Vanderbilt House, undated (Box 340)
      - Gertrude Rhinelander Waldo Mansion, 1997 (Box 340)
      - Mrs. Graham Fair Vanderbilt House, 1978-1979 and undated (Box 340)
      - Henry T. Sloane residence, 1966 and undated (Box 340)
      - Hotel Theresa, undated (Box 340)
      - James Watson House (part of the Shrine of Blessed Elizabeth Seton), undated (Box 340)
      - Loew's Paradise Theater, undated (Box 340)
      - Manhasset Apartments, undated (Box 340)
      - Manhattan Company Building, undated (Box 340)
      - Messiah Home for Children, undated (Box 340)
      - Mother African Methodist Episcopal Zion Church, undated (Box 340)
      - New designation list 9/97, 1997-1998 (Box 340)
      - New York Public Library, Aguilar Branch, undated (Box 340)
      - New York Public Library, Tottenville Branch, undated (Box 340)
      - New York Training School for Teachers, undated (Box 340)
      - Number 8 Thomas Street Building, undated (Box 340)
      - Panhellenic Tower, 1998 (Box 340)
      - Photocopies from book, with entries on designated historic landmarks, 1993 (Box 340)
      - Pike Street Synagogue, undated (Box 340)
      - Research sources, undated (Box 340)
      - Saint Philip's Protestant Episcopal Church, undated (Box 340)
      - Schermerhorn Row, 1968 and undated (Box 340)
      - Schinasi Residence, undated (Box 341)
      - Schomburg Collection for Research in Black Culture (originally West 35th Street Branch Library), undated (Box 341)
      - Scribner Building, 1987 (Box 341)
      - Charles Scribner's Building, 1992 (Box 341)
      - Sea and Land Church, 1987 and undated (Box 341)
      - Seagram Building, M circa 1956-1958, 1992 (Box 341)
      - J. and W. Seligman and Company Building, undated (Box 341)
      - Shively Sanitary Apartments, 1988 (Box 341)
      - The Shubert Theater, 1988 (Box 341)
      - Sidewalk Clock, 1981 and undated (Box 341)
      - Sniffen Court, 1966 and undated (Box 341)
      - SoHo Cast Iron, 1973 and undated, 2 folders (Box 341)
      - South Street Seaport, 1987 and undated (Box 341)
      - Spanish and Portuguese Synagogue, 1987 and undated (Box 341)
      - Squadron A Armory, undated (Box 341)
      - Standard Oil Building, undated (Box 341)
      - Starrett-Lehigh Building, 1987 and undated (Box 341)
      - Statue of Liberty, 1986-1987 and undated (Box 341)
      - Stephen Van Rensselaer House, 1987 (Box 341)
      - Street plan of New Amsterdam and Colonial New York, 1983 and undated (Box 341)
      - Stuyvesant Fish House, undated (Box 341)
      - Stuyvesant High School, undated (Box 341)
      - Stuyvesant Square, 1975 and undated (Box 341)
      - Sullivan Street Houses, 1973 and undated (Box 341)
      - The Sun Building, 1987 and undated (Box 341)
      - Trinity Church and Graveyard, 1987 (Box 341)
      - Turtle Bay Gardens Historic District, undated (Box 341)
      - Tweed Courthouse, 1987 (Box 341)
      - Union Square Savings Bank, undated (Box 341)
      - Union Theological Seminary, undated (Box 341)
      - United States Courthouse, 1987 (Box 341)
      - United States Customs House, 1966-1991 (Box 342)
      - United States Federal Building, undated (Box 342)
      - United States General Post Office, 1987 and undated (Box 342)
      - United States Realty Building, 1988 and undated (Box 342)
      - University Club, 1987 (Box 342)
      - Upper East Side, 1984-1987 (Box 342)
      - Villard Houses, 1968, 1987 (Box 342)
      - Wadleigh School, undated (Box 342)
      - Watch Tower, undated (Box 342)
      - Water Tower, undated (Box 342)
      - West End Collegiate, 1974 and 1987 (Box 342)
      - West 24th Street houses, 1970, 1987 and undated (Box 342)
      - West 54th Street houses, 1981-1987 and undated (Box 342)
      - West End Avenue, 1987 and undated (Box 342)
      - West End Collegiate School and Church, undated (Box 342)
      - Western Union Building, 1991 (Box 342)
      - Payne Whitney House, 1970, 1987 and undated (Box 342)
      - Willard Straight House/International Center for Photography, 1975, 1987 and undated (Box 342)
      - Willett Street Methodist Church/ Bialystoker Synagogue, undated (Box 342)
      - Woods Mercantile Buildings, undated (Box 342)
    - WWOR Television Network, 1990; 19
      - Contract, 1990 (Box 342)
      - List of video available, and drafts of texts, 1990 (Box 342)
      - Shooting script, detailed, and correspondence, 1990 (Box 342)
      - Shooting script draft, 1990 (Box 342)
      - Video shooting script and log sheets, circa 1990, folder 1 of 3 (Box 342)
      - Video shooting script and log sheets, circa 1990, folders 2-3 of 3 (Box 343)
  - Buildings Reborn, 1880s-1985; 5
    Materials from major projects centering on the re-adaptive use of historical buildings in the United States, which culminated in a series of nationally-acclaimed books and related exhibits: Buildings Reborn (first volume published in 1979), and Remaking America (first volume published in 1986). Formats in the project files include correspondence, printed materials (including many articles and clippings), photographs, color slides, clippings, photocopies, drafts, notes, and general working files. Earliest materials are research copies and are dated based on content rather than date of creation.
    Subseries is divided further into Book, Exhibition, General Working Files, and Research Files; folders are arranged alphabetically by title. Original folder titles have been retained. There is considerable overlap between materials in the General Working Files subseries of Buildings Reborn and Remaking America.
    - Book, 1975-1981; 20
      - Acknowledgements and credits, 1979 (Box 343)
      - Arts exposition conference book fair, 1981 (Box 343)
      - Balance House, LTD contract, 1977-1978 (Box 343)
      - Built to last, 1977 (Box 343)
      - Book correspondence requests, 1976-1979 (Box 343)
      - Description of your project form letter, sent by Diamonstein-Spielvogel to participants, undated (Box 343)
      - Draft, undated (Box 343)
      - Drafts, edits, notes, undated, 2 folders (Box 343)
      - Final drafts, 1985 (Box 343)
      - Follow-up calls, important, 1978 (Box 343)
      - Front matter pictures not used, 1977 and undated (Box 343)
      - Gallery Association, article, 1978 (Box 343)
      - Gallery Association, article, 1978, 1 oversize poster (Box 384)
      - Harper & Row press release, 1978 (Box 344)
      - Index lists, 1977, 2 folders (Box 344)
      - Letters from mayors, 1977 (Box 344)
      - Letters to members, Board of Directors, Landmarks Conservancy, undated (Box 344)
      - Letters from Brademas, 1977 (Box 344)
      - Lists, index cards, placeholders, 1975-1977 (Box 344)
      - Manuscript drafts, 1978, 1-4 of 8 folders (Box 344)
      - Manuscript drafts, 1978, 5-8 of 8 folders (Box 345)
      - Manuscript drafts, 1978, 3 oversize photographs with notes (Box 383)
      - Memory's Anchor, Introduction, undated (Box 345)
      - Memory's Anchor, Original, undated (Box 345)
      - Negatives, undated, 21 sets of oversize negatives and 1 letter (Box 383)
      - New York Landmarks Conservancy, 1972-1977 (Box 345)
      - New York symposium transcript, undated (Box 345)
      - Permissions, 1978 (Box 345)
      - Photographs of historic landmarks, for book illustrations, black-and-white, undated, 2 folders (Box 346)
      - Photograph captioning notes, undated (Box 346)
      - Preface, 1979 (Box 346)
      - Preface draft, 1978 (Box 346)
      - Preface draft, undated, 2 folders (Box 346)
      - Press information extra copies, 1978-1980 (Box 346)
      - Press materials, 1978-1985 (Box 346)
      - Press materials, 1978-1985, oversize poster (Box 384)
      - Publisher's Weekly, 1978 (Box 346)
      - Richard Haas, artist - article draft about his murals, undated (Box 604)
      - Royalty statements, 1980 (Box 346)
      - Scribner's, 1977 (Box 346)
      - Selected bibliography, 1979 (Box 346)
      - Slides (color) From NY Department of Cultural Affairs presentation, 1978 (Box 346)
    - Exhibition, 1968-1982; 21
      - At Fraunces Tavern Museum, 1980 (Box 347)
      - Budget, 1978 (Box 347)
      - Budget - food, 1978-1979 (Box 347)
      - Central Grammar Apartment, Gloucester, Massachusetts, 1978 (Box 347)
      - Citizen's Bank, Las Cruces, New Mexico, undated (Box 347)
      - Cooper Hewitt/Lisa Taylor, 1977 (Box 347)
      - Chicago, 1978 (Box 347)
      - Chicago Public Library Cultural Center, undated (Box 347)
      - Cookie place cards, circa 1980, (8x6 and 12x10 in.) (Box 622)
      - Correspondence, notes, lists, proposals, 1978 (Box 347)
        Includes a numbered master list of the Buildings Reborn projects.
      - Correspondence, notes, lists, proposals, 1978: oversize booklet (Box 383)
      - Description, 1978 and undated (Box 347)
      - Detroit Cornice and State Building, Detroit, Michigan, 1978 (Box 347)
      - Don Hix at torpedo factory studio, Alexandria, Virginia (photo), undated (Box 347)
      - Drafts (exhibition), 1978, 3 folders (Box 347)
      - Edward Mooney House, New York, New York, 1978 (Box 347)
      - Faneuil Hall, Boston, Massachusetts, 1876 (reproduction), 1976-1978 (Box 347)
      - Form letter, 1978 (Box 347)
      - Form letter for museums scheduled to show, 1981 (Box 347)
      - Forms for donors of objects, undated (Box 347)
      - Gallery Association of New York State (Trudy), 1977 (Box 347)
      - General, 1976-1978, 2 folders (Box 347)
      - Ghirardelli Square, San Francisco, California, 1966-1978 (Box 348)
      - Ghirardelli Square, 1966-1978, oversize drawing (Box 383)
      - Great Halls Historical District, Paterson, New Jersey, 1978 (Box 348)
      - Helena, Montana, 1968, 1978, and undated (Box 348)
      - Howard Library, New Orleans, Louisiana, 1977-1978 (Box 348)
      - Immovable Objects (exhibition), 1978 (Box 348)
        Exhibition, sponsored by Cooper-Hewitt Museum, first shown in 1975, and focused on the design and architecture of public spaces such as playgrounds, plazas, and pedestrian malls.
      - Institute of Contemporary Art, Boston, Massachusetts, 1978 (Box 348)
      - Jamaica Arts Center, Jamaica, New York, undated (Box 348)
      - Jefferson Market Court House, New York, New York, 1978 (Box 348)
      - Kansas City, Missouri, 1970-1980, 2 folders (Box 348)
      - List of Reborn exhibition projects, undated (Box 348)
      - Lutheran Medical Center, Brooklyn, New York, undated (Box 348)
      - Marshall Lee notes, 1978 (Box 348)
      - Master list, preface, undated (Box 348)
      - Memos, 1977-1978 and undated (Box 348)
      - Miscellaneous invitations, undated (Box 348)
      - Miscellaneous public relations, 1978-1981 (Box 348)
      - Mount Royal Station, Baltimore, Maryland, undated (Box 349)
      - Museum of City of New York press release, undated (Box 349)
      - Museum of Contemporary Art, Bristol, Rhode Island, undated (Box 349)
      - National Collection of Fine Arts, Washington, D.C., 1978 (Box 349)
      - National Endowment for the Arts, 1977 (Box 349)
      - Navy Pier, Chicago, Illinois, 1978 (Box 349)
      - New Uses, Old Places symposium registration, undated (Box 349)
      - Norfolk Chamber of Commerce, Norfolk, Virginia, 1978 (Box 349)
      - Old Carter Dry Goods Company, undated (Box 349)
      - Old Market District, Omaha, Nebraska, 1978 (Box 349)
      - Old Market District, 1978, oversize photograph with notes (Box 383)
      - Opening reception - invitees lists, 1978 (Box 349)
      - Original edited exhibition scripts, 1978 (Box 349)
      - Panel 5 one-liners: A. Community Arts Center, B. Howard Library, C. Department of Pensions and Security, D. Appraiser's Warehouse, 1975 and undated (Box 349)
      - Panel 6 one-liners: A. Chamber of Commerce Building, B. Clinton House, C. Edward Mooney House, D. Great Falls Historic District, 1969 and undated (Box 349)
      - Panel 7 one-liners: A. Citizens Bank, B. Will Reuben Thomas Center, C. Jefferson Market Library, D. Schlegal Corporation Headquarters, D. HMS Queen Mary, undated (Box 349)